{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/2242","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2242","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"7201 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48214","owner":"Copeland TH inc","licenseNumber":"081044","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.00183,42.34762","geojson":{"id":"2242","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.001828983,42.347621957]},"properties":{"name":"Tim Hortons","owner":"Copeland TH inc","address":"7201 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48214","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"081044","establishmentid":"2242","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2094","name":"Salvation Army Evangeline Center","address":"130 Grand Blvd. W.","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4538","name":"Continental Canteen","address":"130 E. Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5054","name":"Belle Isle Krispy Crunchy Chicken","address":"7255 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"4819","name":"Miami Fish & Chicken, LLC","address":"7255  Jefferson E.","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"51623632","name":"Nicky D's","address":"6931 Jefferson E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1188","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #345","address":"6931 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3097","name":"Church's Fried Chicken","address":"6931 Jefferson St. E.","zipcode":"48213"},{"establishmentid":"2332","name":"City Pekins Chinese Food","address":"6905 Jefferson E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1882","name":"City Pekin Chinese Food","address":"6905 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2257","name":"SNACK-A-LOT VENDING","address":"7601 JEFFERSON E.","zipcode":"48219"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"56951","inspectionDate":"2022-01-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In dishwash area","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hand sink in same room as dish handling."},{"violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WAREWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Under the Three compartment sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"54690","inspectionDate":"2021-01-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Display","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"On the floor Debris","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DRIVE-THRU WINDOW","subLocation":"At the Sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Faucet","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53542","inspectionDate":"2020-12-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"50879","inspectionDate":"2020-01-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (small)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44953","inspectionDate":"2019-01-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"old/broken equipment","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"insects","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"41345","inspectionDate":"2018-01-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Hot holding drawer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"On top of the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"doors","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (small)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Under the Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"To the left of Dumpster(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37936","inspectionDate":"2017-02-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Under the Ice bin","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2242"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}